Prophet T.B. Joshua arrives in Paraguay.
Arrival Of Prophet T.B. Joshua In Preparation For
Crusade Paraguay with T.B. Joshua
Del Pilar Medina de Paredes Secretary General Of The Parliament For Paraguay
She is a senator.
She is very pleased to receive the Prophet T.B. Joshua here in Paraguay.
I'm very excited and I can see a lot of expectation in the people from Paraguay
because they are waiting for a spiritual transformation through the coming of this messenger from Christ.
All of us are waiting for that spiritual transformation.
We want to receive him very well; we want to be healed and
as a member of parliament, I appreciate his coming.
We are a privileged nation to have him visit our country.
His visit will also contribute to the National Police.
I'm very glad and I know that this spiritual expectation of our Paraguayan people
for healing and family transformation will come to pass.
Together with my colleague, Bernardo Villaba, we are members of the National Parliament
and we came to welcome and appreciate the man of God for his coming to Paraguay.
In our nation, there is a lot of hope and expectation.
I am honoured to be a part of the welcoming committee
as a representative from the national government.
They are very grateful.
They are representing the politics here in Paraguay.
They are very blessed.
I cannot to see the prophet, to receive healing and to receive the strength I need.
Thank you very much.
Many dignitaries came to the Silvio Pettirossi international airport
to honour the arrival of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Among them was Del Pilar Medina, a member of parliament and parliamentary secretary,
representing the government of Paraguay, as well as the national police delegation.
General Commissioner of police, William Gimenez and Commissioner of police, Jose Felix Vega
also welcomed Prophet T.B. Joshua at the airport.
The doors are open; this is your house.
If there is anything you need, we are at your service – on behalf of our institution.
We have a lot of respect and admiration for you.
Welcome.
Thank you for coming.
You are bringing peace through faith so that we can have prosperity
and especially healing to our institution.
Thank you.
We are at your service.
May God bless you.
You are a blessing to us.
General Commissioner Of Police, William Gimenez And Commissioner Of Police, Jose Felix Vega Receive Prophet T.B. Joshua In Paraguay
Prophet T.B. Joshua I Warmly Welcomed To The Nation Of Paraguay
Prophet T.B. Joshua is warmly welcomed on this historic visit to Paraguay by crowd of people
who have come to receive the Prophet in great anticipation of what God is about to do in their nation.
As the crowd cheer on, the man of God is also welcomed by a group
of Paraguayan traditional dancers.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Is Welcomed By A Group Of Paraguayan Traditional Dancers
Prophet T.B. Joshua makes his way to the awaiting vehicle and the crowd follow him,
not wanting to miss a moment.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Is Warmly Welcomed To The Nation Of Paraguay
The crowd continue to cheer in appreciation to God for bringing His Prophet to their nation.
Their hearts overflow with joy, knowing that thousands of lives will be changed through a revival in Paraguay.
The evidence of Jesus Christ is lives that are changed,
and indeed, the nation of Paraguay will never be the same again.
Prophet T.B. Joshua's Arrival In The Nation Of Paraguay
One of the top prestigious newspapers in Paraguay, on Thursday, the 10th of August 2017
featured Prophet T.B. Joshua in their article titled,
"Nigerian Preacher, TB Joshua, Awarded Paraguay's Highest Honour – The National Order Of Merit"
The national Parliament of Paraguay has concurred to grant the "Comuneros" National Order of Merit
to Nigerian Prophet TB Joshua.
This was decided August 9th 2017, at the sitting of Parliament in Asuncion,
according to 970 AM Radio journalist, Nativida Romero.
Member of Parliament Bernardo Villalba (ANR) proposed
that the spiritual leader, Temitope Balogun Joshua, receive the highest distinction
the Parliament can bestow.
The legislator's proposal was fully approved.
Avanze Pais MP, Rocio Casco, did however oppose it on the ground that the distinction had previously
only been awarded to citizens of the country.
For his part, the legislator Villalba maintained his position.
Villalba put forward his arguments, in full session, where he expressed that Joshua,
compelled to visit Paraguay, "will bring peace and blessing to the population."
"I do not just want to welcome him to our country. We pray his stay be as fruitful as possible and that it will be
a blessing to our nation.
For the first time ever, I propose the National Order to be awarded to a personality and I am proposing that
he be awarded this distinction by the Members of Parliament," said Villalba.
Villalba solicited the preacher be presented the national honour at the Defensores del Chaco Stadium,
where he will host the crusade.
The National Parliament Of Paraguay, Asuncion
EXCLUSIVE: T.B. Joshua Arrives In Paraguay, Awarded National Honour